export const cssQNA = [
    {
        questionText: "Q.1 Whats Box Model in CSS & Which CSS Properties are part of it ?",
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/css-qa#heading-q1-whats-the-box-model-in-css-amp-which-css-properties-are-part-of-it'
    },
    {
        questionText: "Q.2 What are the Different Types of Selectors in CSS & what are the advantages of them?",
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/css-qa#heading-q2-what-are-the-different-types-of-selectors-in-css-amp-what-are-their-advantages-of-them'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.3 What is VW/VH & How its different from PX?',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/css-qa#heading-q3-what-is-vw-vh-amp-how-its-different-from-px'
    },{
        questionText: "Q.4 Whats difference between Inline, Inline Block and block ?",
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/css-qa#heading-q4-what-is-the-difference-between-inline-inline-block-and-block'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.5 How is Border-box different from Content Box?',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/css-qa#heading-q5-how-is-the-border-box-different-from-the-content-box'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.6 What’s z-index and How does it Function ?',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/css-qa#heading-q6-what-is-z-index-and-how-does-it-function'
    },{
        questionText: "Q.7 What’s Grid & Flex and difference between them?",
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/css-qa#heading-q7-what-are-grid-amp-flex-and-the-difference-between-them'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.8 Difference between absolute and relative and sticky and fixed position explain with example.',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/css-qa#heading-q8-difference-between-absolute-and-relative-and-sticky-and-fixed-positions-explain-with-an-example'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.9 Build Periodic Table as shown in the below image',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/css-qa#heading-q9-build-a-periodic-table-as-shown-in-the-below-image'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.10. Build given layout using grid or flex see below image for reference.',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/css-qa#heading-q10-build-the-given-layout-using-grid-or-flex-see-the-below-image-for-reference'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.11. Build Responsive Layout both desktop and mobile and Tablet, see below image for reference ?',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/css-qa#heading-q11-build-a-responsive-layout-for-both-desktop-and-mobile-and-tablet-see-the-below-image-for-reference'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q. 12. Build Complete Homepage of Ineuron ( Link ) with responsiveness.',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/css-qa#heading-q12-build-a-complete-homepage-of-ineuron-with-responsiveness-linkhttpsineuronai'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.13. What are Pseudo-classes in CSS & How is it different From Pseudo Elements?',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/css-qa#heading-q13-what-are-pseudo-classes-in-css-amp-how-is-it-different-from-pseudo-elements'
    },
]